# What will you do today?
# What are you gonna do today?
# I'm going to do this, you're going to fall on me #
# What are you gonna do?
# Let's get around the operation
Staff, how long do you think it'll take you to get here?
Bamboo!
Bamboo stomp!
Bamboo, green bamboo!
I'll bring bamboo!
I'll bring bamboo to the provinces!
What will you do today?
Please! Thank you!
I'm Daisuke Nakayama! Pleased to meet you!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
♪ What are you gonna do today?
I thought if I didn't eat fried food on the first day.
Don't eat fried food.
# What are you gonna do today?
♪ What are you gonna do today?
It started on the radio, something like that,
It started with a radio segment called Epitude, where they wanted to do something like this.
And then I got the blue tongue, and that's when I started.
You know, to get me excited or something.
Yes, I meditate, so I calm down.
I don't want to go on stage like that.
I said I want to move my body.
That's all.
Thank you very much. Nakayama time.
What are you going to do today?
Ready!
Move your hair, move your feet, let's go!
One, two, three, four, five.
Is that me today? I'm all alone.
Oh, you're not?
Duck.
Oh, you're a sucker.
That's why I'm feeling so vulnerable today.
♪ I'll tell you what to do ♪
# Action uplifted
♪ Happy homeland
Okay, next win, five, three, three, seven, eight. Let's go!
Let's go!
♪ Knock-knock, knock-knock ♪
Everybody together.
♪ All together, all together
Let's keep it going till the end and enjoy it till the end!
♪ What will you do today?
And, oh, well, stop your heart
I'm free today, too.
But I can't connect with you again
We'll live together
Only really.
Don't worry about the adults
I'm gonna have to take this. It's too late for that.
I don't need any more of that motivational support energy.
I need to calm down.
Wow. Seltzer soda.
I'm calm. I'm calm. I'm calm.
I want a soda.
I don't know. I think I'll have a Coke.
But Coke is full of sugar
I'll have a Fanta
Fanta has a lot of sugar.
I want to drink a lot of soda.
The end of the last one...
Yes. Thank you very much.
Not here. Not here.
Was anyone here? Not here.
Stay tuned for the next video!
Please subscribe to our channel!